qvo6.com 2013-12-19

# Qvo6.com

### Privacy Policy

Magic Forever Technology Limited. owns and operates a number of different sites on the Web. Qvo6 is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information Qvo6 may gather about individuals who visit the Qvo6 Sites,how that information is used,and Qvo6 's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to the Qvo6 Sites,and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links or to any software that may be downloaded from the Qvo6 Sites.

### What types of information do we collect?

Each time you visit the Site,we collect the limited information that your browser makes available whenever you visit any website. This information includes: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address;(b) the address of the last URL you visited before clicking through to the Site;(c) your browser and platform type;(d) your browser language;and (e) the data in any undeleted "cookies" that your browser previously accepted from us. Additionally,when you enter a search query using the Site or Services,we will receive the query text and process it,together with the above data,to return a search results page to you. If you have modified your browser settings so that address-bar search queries and erroneous domain name system (DNS) requests are submitted to us,we may also receive any search query or misspelled URL that you enter into your browser's address bar.

The Site and Services generally do not require registration or submission of an account name or email address in order to use them. However,we may offer certain Services for which registration,including the provision of an account name and email address,is required in order to be fully utilized. You would also need to provide us your email address if you submit a help request or other communication via email. The amount of information that you choose to disclose to us is completely up to you,although access to or use of some Services may be affected if information is not provided.

### Information Storage and Security

We have implemented and use a variety of industry accepted physical,electronic and managerial policies and procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect to help prevent unauthorized access,disclosure,alteration or destruction and to maintain its accuracy and correct use. We generally store the information and data we collect on our own servers in a secure environment and restrict access to your personal information to employees and agents who need to know that information in order to provide you with access and use of other Sites and our services,operate and maintain the Qvo6 Sites and as otherwise set forth and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. While we have taken efforts to safeguard and secure your personal information,we cannot guarantee that your information may not be disclosed,altered or destroyed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.

### PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

Qvo6.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We may notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your information by sending a notice to you,although we are not required to do so,or we may simply place a notice on the Site. Notwithstanding the foregoing,we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without any notice whatsoever to you and for whatever reason we deem appropriate under the circumstances. Your continued use of the Site and our services will be construed as your acceptance of any such change. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect,how we use it,and to whom we disclose it.

### Contact

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy,please contact us and we will endeavor to respond to your request within a reasonable period of time. You may also submit questions or comments using the postal address listed below:  
Magic Forever Technology Limited.  
Mail: Unit 10,16/F,SummerSet Building,No.42 Kannan Street  
Email:[sales@qvo6.com](mailto:sales@qvo6.com)
